Hey friends, welcome to your
channel Tech Smart Minute Friends, in today's
video we will learn about such EM
jobless people, how much commission do they get,
when we make LIC bill payment,
how much commission do we get in premium payment
and how do we do it,
after subscribing you have to
subscribe,
subscribe, the
appointed commission,
we have to click here, it
says Owaisi number, we will enter it here
and below you have to enter the mobile number,
you can enter someone's mobile number here, on
Thursday there is a
customer, you have to enter his name here, you have to appoint a
commissioner,
subscribe,
subscribe
and
click here,
see here all these school options have
come here and everything has been paid and it has been
completed and you can see here, here
our such and such will be visible here and it is
of LIC, you will find it here, if you
want to do it, you can do it and
download it, you
get commission, to reduce it, it goes
to the wallet,
click here, you
can see, you had
not subscribed,
I will show you
[Music] Yes,
see this one  All this was presented by the team of Elaichi,
I will show you how much commission you get in this, in this
also the same commission means on the financial service portal, no matter how much the
premium amount is,
you will get commission on the commission, you will get only the attendance money,
we can see here Anjali
knew that yours was this much and after that
we got this commission, I have
not received the attendance money, so right now in the digital
service, the serial does not get any commission
till the payment of Elaichi is made, so I wanted to
show a little bit of this, if you liked it then
please subscribe to our channel,
thank you